Python Developer | Data Engineer

MACIEJ GAJEWSKI-KALAGA

EXPERIENCE

Brytlyt, Remote

Junior Data Engineer / Python Developer | since May 2020

[{ "point": "Responsible for developing ETL pipelines with Python" }, { "point": "Automating solutions with Python & Bash scripting" }, { "point": "R&D of new technologies (Airflow, Kubernetes)" }, { "point": "Database testing and management (PostgreSQL)" }, { "point": "Working in a dockerized environment on remote Linux servers" }]

Billennium / LOT Polish Airlines, Warsaw

IT Service Desk Specialist | November 2019 - April 2020

[{ "point": "Responsible for providing customer support for company employees" }, { "point": "Active Directory and JIRA management" }, { "point": "Hardware maintainence" }, { "point": "Working in a Microsoft Windows environment" }]

East Asia & Australia

Globetrotter | April 2016 - April 2019

[{ "point": "Hitchhiking from Poland to Australia" }, { "point": "Teaching English in Vietnam" }, { "point": "Volunteering in various places" }]

EDUCATION

[{ "point": "Python programming -> NumPy, Pandas, Matplotlib, Scikit-Learn, Keras, Spark" }, { "point": "Data manipulation, analysis and visualisation" }, { "point": "Statistics and predictive machine learning algorithms" }]

Data Science Bootcamp | October 2019 - November 2020

[{ "point": "Bachelor of Engineering" }, { "point": "Learning math, statistics, physics, geology" }]
Petroleum Engineering | October 2011 - February 2015

SKILLS

About me

Passionate problem-solver who uses leading edge technology solutions with desire to automate everything. Focused on developing reliable software, maintaining complex systems, designing ETL pipelines. Has experience in Data Engineering and DevOps mindset. Recently interested in Web and Cloud Technologies to gain more general Software Engineering experience.